<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MoonX</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="todayTv">Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit ontacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit</string>
    <string name="lunar_response_category_tv">Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profitPlan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and meetings in accordance with the lunar events to gain the most profit. Plan your negotiations, contacts and</string>
    <string name="birth_date_key">birth_date</string>
    <string name="birth_time_key">birth_time</string>
    <string name="welcome">Sed ut perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusam.Sed ut perspt perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error si.</string>
</resources>